Phone. (+1) 416-452-2251 Email. <u>seulah.lee@gmail.com</u>

Seulah Lee

SUMMARY

I am a UX designer with strong product thinking skills and user research skills. I have end-to-end product design experience in both agile and waterfall environment. I can manage details in a complex product and tactically drive a project to delivery by collaborating with engineers, visual designers and product owners.

EXPERIENCE

UX Designer for Naver Map, NAVER | Jungja, South Korea | May 2017 - June 2019

- Managed Bookmarks feature on Naver Map as senior product designer, by creating new features as well as improving existing features based on users' feedback and data
- Worked on complete redesign of Naver Map from concept to execution, responsible for creating new contextual features and defining user flow for the entire app including redesigning home, search results, and places' information pages
 - Communicating design decisions by creating briefs, story maps, user journeys, screen flows, wireframes, and high/low-fidelity prototypes and by conducting user researches for future releases

Product Designer for exeLab, Kakao | Pangyo, South Korea | Oct 2014 - March 2017

- Led web-based media-related projects in a team based on agile/lean UX methodologies, including Daum Entertainment's new service called "My Star," by creating user flows, wireframes, and prototypes
- Created memorial websites for Daum News, such as the one-year anniversary of Sewol ferry disaster and the 20th
 anniversary of Sampoong department store disaster, by generating concepts and narratives as well as creating wireframes for
 responsive design

UX Designer/Researcher, Daum Communications | Seoul, South Korea | July 2012 - Oct 2014

- Created a new mobile service for Buzz Launcher, from consolidating a concept to creating wireframes, in a fast-paced collaborative environment
- · Conducted user researches and delivered wireframes for web services, such as shopping and payment
- Conducted preliminary market and user researches for Internet of Things industry and mobile instant messenger services in Southeast Asia

UX Researcher, Synovate Korea | Seoul, South Korea | March 2010 - June 2011

Planned, designed, and conducted qualitative researches related to product usability, design development, and user experience in Korea and North America for Samsung Electronics

- Preliminary user research for media consumption and motivation for content creation (2011)
- User/market research for multiscreen strategy and for device-to-service convergence strategy (2010-2011)
- Mobile phones' virtual keypad and Smart TV UI usability test (2011) etc.

EDUCATION

University of Toronto | 2019-Present Master of Information candidate

Brooklyn Law School | 2009 J.D. Withdrawn in good standing

University of Toronto | 2003-2007 Honours Bachelor of Arts with Distinction, Major: International Relations, Asia-Pacific Studies

ACHIEVEMENTS & SKILLS

Patent registered "Method For Controlling Presentation Of Contents and User Device For Performing The Method" (Korea, No.10-1685288)

Proficiency in a variety of design tools such as Sketch, Principle, Framer, and InVision

Familiar with Adobe Photoshop, Adobe After Effects and basics of HTML and CSS

Fluent in Korean and English; conversant in Japanese

REFERENCES

Dong-Kyun, Kang Senior UX designer at Samsung Electronics T. 82-10-3200-4115

Jong-Hak, Kim UX leader at Kakao Al T. 82-10-4441-8534